Aki-sama's late.
It's quite hot today, isn't it?
Do you happen to know
where Masamune-sama is?
Why ask me?
I surmised you were the first
person whom I should ask.
I don't know.
Is that so?
Yes.
Oh, I see.
#6: "Attack! Battle of the Home Visits"
Well, for example...
You could kiss me.
Kiss...
To osculate...
A smooch...
What? If you actually liked me,
you could at least do that.
W-Well, um...
D-Don't be ridiculous!
A k-k-k-k-k-kiss was, like, the last of
the last of the "Dead or Love" Plan.
I was planning it as the grand finale!
Makabe...
I love you.
But I refuse!
Mission complete!
That's the last scene.
And so, for this to happen at
such a random, unpopular point,
and right in the middle of my plan,
was completely unaccounted for!
See? I knew it.
I don't have time for this.
Wait!
What are you doing,
grabbing onto her like that?!
You just dove right into the main event!
It's insane! This is insane!
But I can't run away from
this. What should I...
I know. This is a ham!
She's a ham shaped like a person!
If I think of it as biting into a tasty
ham I got as a midsummer gift...
H-Hey!
No! Don't!
What'd you do that for?!
B-But...
Don't "but" me!
There's no use in acting like the
victim here, you stupid ham!
Oh, Masamune-kun?
Huh? Class Rep?
What are you doing there?
One of the teachers made us
clean the pool as punishment,
and the pool seemed so nice and cool,
we couldn't help but splash right in.
What the heck?
Still, you probably shouldn't
dive in with your clothes on.
L-Looks like I managed to
dodge that bullet for now...
What are you doing here, Class Rep?
Me? I have practice.
So she's in the swim club, too.
That's why she's got such
a nice cardio body.
Well, good luck with the cleaning.
Th-Thanks...
What the hell? You're trying to escape?
Well...
I guess I'll just accept the fact
that you love me so much,
you have no idea what to do with yourself.
And that brings up the question: "So what?"
You can't be serious!
Someone fry that ham to a crisp!
What the hell is her problem?
She's the one who told me to do it.
I actually tried to kiss her.
There you are, Masamune-sama.
Fujinomiya-san?!
I've been looking for you.
I don't think I have the energy
to hang out right now...
My, you must be tired
from that grueling task.
You can have this, if you like.
Hot tea? At this time of year?
It's salty.
I hear it's best to never let your body
get a chill, even in the summer.
I also hear you need sodium and
citric acid to fight dehydration.
So I thought the best solution would be
roasted green tea with pickled plum in it.
Huh...
Well, that makes sense.
I prefer this over some
disgustingly sweet juice.
The other things you lack are
essential vitamins and magnesium.
Beer yeast and propolis.
Multivitamin
Magnesium
This company's propolis has
a patented method for how
it's absorbed into your body,
making it more effective.
Then there's the magnesium and...
I-I'm terribly sorry! I've been presumptuous.
I can't say that I'm very fond
of turning to medicines first.
Exercise and diet are more important.
I think it's fine to use medicines
as an aid after that, but...
Of course, I do believe that's ideal.
She's pretty cute when she's
pouting like that, too.
Fujinomiya-san, can I ask you something?
Yes?
What do you like about me?
I'm definitely a guy who can
turn even a stumble into profit!
This is the super difficult question Adagaki
Aki posed to me that I couldn't answer.
What is there to like about me?
I'll immediately shoot down any superficial
answers like "your face" or "everything!"
And of course, since you don't know me,
you can't give a real answer
about my character.
It's the best question to ask, since either
answer allows me to easily shoot her down!
So, how are you going to answer?
I like how you're so modest that you
don't even realize your own charms.
White...
Whitening!
I-I see.
You should be a little more confident,
because you're a very lovely
person, Masamune-sama.
That woman is a tougher than I thought.
I get it! I think what I'm lacking is the
ability to be unreasonably audacious.
Oh, my pants are almost dry.
That commando girl is definitely dangerous.
I need to cut her down from the roots.
Where is she going off to on her own?
This is...
What's that woman thinking?
Did you need something from Neko-sama?
I-I have no idea what you're talking about.
Shidou. She's an acquaintance of mine.
Koiwai Yoshino-san.
You work as Adagaki-sama's
attendant, don't you?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I don't know.
You can stop with the charade.
I know it's your job, but it must be difficult.
Why are you so concerned
with Makabe Masamune?
Because he saved me in the past.
You're lying. I heard
everything from Pig's Foot.
May I help you two?
The way I'm so modest that I don't
even realize my own charms, huh...
I'll use that line the next
time I see Adagaki Aki.
But if I keep admiring her like this,
I'm going to keep falling for her.
I'm home.
Right. First, pick up the shrimp...
Like this?
What's all the ruckus?
Yes, that's right!
Yes, keep that up.
Very good! Next, we have the eggs.
Oh, Maa-kun. Welcome home.
Welcome home, Masamune-sama.
What the hell are you two doing here?!
I tried making fried shrimp
for the first time in my life.
I hope it's to your liking.
O-Oh... I get it.
This isn't my house.
It's almost ready, so nibble on
some cookies while you wait.
But the loli hag is here...
Wait! This is my house!
M-Master!
My hands are all sticky.
That doesn't matter right now!
What the heck is going on?
May I help you two?
Those uniforms! You must
go to Maa-kun's school.
Were you looking for Maa-kun?
Are you Maa-kun's fans?
Maa-kun is so popular!
Maa-kun isn't home yet. Come on in.
I was planning to make fried shrimp tonight.
Er, no, I'm okay.
E-B-I! Otherwise known as shrimp!
Shrimp!
You, too! Repeat after me!
No, I'm afraid I have work to do.
I-I'm so sorry that my
mom can't take a hint.
It was super awkward.
Anyway, I need you guys to leave,
before you see anything dangerous.
Was there anything else?
By "dangerous," do you mean everything here?
Huh? What do you mean?
This room that makes it
obvious that you have
nothing but weight training on your mind.
S-Stop looking around so much!
And call it the "gym machine of perfection"!
Listen up. You can't lose a single day
on the road to becoming a hot guy.
If you let the smallest fat go, it'll
become an even bigger visceral fat.
A single drop of oil is the
beginning of a huge fatty.
My, what a lovely room.
This is all rather ideal for rehabilitation.
Masamune-sama?
It's embarrassing to do that here.
I won't be fooled, no matter
what weird things you say!
Did you need something?
Oh, yes. The shrimp is ready.
Chinatsu-sama also just came home,
so Kinue-sama is waiting for you.
High in Calories
Such high calories again...
Man, I was so surprised.
I can't believe you actually have friends
willing to come over, Onii-chan.
Oh, why is that?
Masamune-sama is quite popular.
Well, Onii-chan's scared of
people finding out who—
Is this the stupid mouth
that's blabbing too much?!
"Who"? You mean Masamune-sama?
Oh, yeah. I mean, he thinks
he's hot stuff now, but—
And that's enough idle chatter! Let's eat!
Why are you sitting here? There's no room.
Did everyone take a seat?
All right, let's eat.
This breading is pretty much all fat.
Jeez!
Maa-kun, Neko-chan! Don't do that!
You're supposed to enjoy your meals!
Enjoy?
But calories are a problem.
Nutrients are important.
You two are so much alike.
Hey, I'm not gonna let that slide!
Why?
"Why," nothing! How are we alike at all?
Yoshino-chan, there's more if you'd like.
Okay.
Hey, let's set off some fireworks after we eat.
Hey! Stop deciding for everyone else!
They're both really busy, you know.
My! Fireworks! How lovely. I would love to!
What about you, Yoshino-san?
Okay.
Yay!
This little...
It's fireworks time!
Did you really have to
change into a yukata?
Fireworks!
You're gonna bother the neighbors.
Fujinomiya-san, hurry! Come here!
Well, good job taking her out
to the yard, my little sister.
It's safer than me being inside
this house with that woman.
Your little sister is pretty
different from you.
She's way too hyper.
Sorry to make you go through with all this.
It's fine. I'm just not very fond of fireworks.
Huh? Why not?
A long time ago,
Aki-sama thought up an experiment
Ten, nine, eight, seven, six,
five, four, three, two, one...
to find out how many rocket fireworks it
would take to fly someone to the moon,
and I was the guinea pig...
My vision went white and
I couldn't hear anymore.
Enough! That's enough, Master!
You don't have to say it!
How sadistic can that Cruel Princess be?!
These snake fireworks are so calming.
I think I'll just leave her be.
Chinatsu-sama, your obi is loose.
Huh?
Th-Thanks.
What are you all red for?
A Chinese peony when she stands,
and a tree peony when she sits, was it?
Thanks.
Chinatsu-sama is very cute.
Is she? I don't think so.
I've never experienced
such a delightful time.
I'm not sure how I should be reacting.
Everyone's set off fireworks before.
It's so beautiful.
Everyone, I sliced some watermelon.
More food?!
Watermelon!
Fujinomiya-san, Koiwai-san,
let's have a contest!
A contest?
For what?
To see who can spit the
seeds the farthest, duh!
I'm not going to lose.
Are they all grade-schoolers?
If you weren't such a liar,
we might have been able to have
a different kind of relationship.
If I didn't have this vendetta
against Adagaki Aki,
would I have felt something else?
Fujinomiya-san, are you done changing?
Your ride is here.
I'll be right there.
She's finally going home.
That was so nerve-wracking.
Masamune-sama.
Won't you see me to my house?
Oh, come on. You have
someone waiting for you.
Today was such a fun day.
I regret that it's over.
Well, that's nice.
Please never come over again.
Farewell.
What about you, Master?
Want me to walk you home?
I live at Aki-sama's place.
R-Right...
I don't want her getting the wrong idea again.
Then I'll just walk you to a main
road where you can get a taxi.
Pig's Foot.
Don't get caught up in her pace.
Wh-What are you talking about?
That's not happening.
No matter what.
Man, that was so much fun!
I feel a little relieved now. I thought
Onii-chan would be alone forever.
Yeah.
To think we'd meet again here...
Fujinomiya-san.
I'm very sorry that I could
not accompany you, milady.
It's quite all right. I was
able to produce some results.
We're alike...
She might be right.
It's the way you're so modest that you
don't even realize your own charms.
Huh?
I just told you how I feel.
Did you think saying that would
stir the slightest feelings in me?
Such a cheap line. I'm not
you, for crying out loud.
Just so you know, I know exactly
what my potential is.
And in your case, it's not that
you're too modest to realize it.
It's just that you're a moron.
Master...
You just stole her line? Are you stupid?